<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rooms on Skurrilum</title>
    <link>https://example.org/en/rooms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rooms on Skurrilum</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/en/rooms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ernie Hudson &amp; The Wailing Woman</title>
      <link>https://example.org/en/the-wailing-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/en/the-wailing-woman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;note-both-ernie-hudson-rooms-can-be-played-independently-of-each-other-and-do-not-require-any-prior-knowledge&#34;&gt;players: &amp;ldquo;4-8 people&amp;rdquo;&#xA;idealPlayers: &amp;ldquo;ideal for 5-6 players&amp;rdquo;&#xA;minAge: &amp;ldquo;from 14 years&amp;rdquo;&#xA;shortDescription: &amp;ldquo;Award-winning radio play adventure in Mrs. Bunbury&amp;rsquo;s villa, searching for a mysterious woman.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;accessibility: &amp;ldquo;This room is not accessible and not suitable for physically impaired players.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;warnings: &amp;ldquo;Stroboscope effects are used.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;note: &amp;ldquo;Both Ernie Hudson rooms can be played independently of each other and do not require any prior knowledge.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Escape Room ‘The Wailing Woman’ is part of our series “Ghost Hunter Ernie Hudson” and is the first mix of escape game and radio play, which was voted 1st Top Escape Room 2018. More than five different locations, an exciting story, and breathtaking effects await in the Escape Room ‘The Wailing Woman’ for all those who have always dreamed of taking the title role in their favorite radio play. Together with the support of ghost hunter Ernie Hudson, you enter the old villa of the frightened Mrs. Bunbury to search for the wailing woman. By solving tricky and exciting puzzles, you will find out what secret lies behind this escape room. ‘The Wailing Woman’ is a unique escape room that is told using radio play elements and requires the finest detective work. Can you uncover the secret of the wailing woman?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ernie Hudson &amp; The Zoo of Death</title>
      <link>https://example.org/zoo-of-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/zoo-of-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;note-both-ernie-hudson-games-can-be-played-independently-and-do-not-require-any-prior-knowledge&#34;&gt;shortTitle: &amp;ldquo;The Zoo of Death&amp;rdquo;&#xA;players: &amp;ldquo;3-6 people&amp;rdquo;&#xA;idealPlayers: &amp;ldquo;ideal for 4 players&amp;rdquo;&#xA;minAge: &amp;ldquo;from 14 years&amp;rdquo;&#xA;shortDescription: &amp;ldquo;Investigate mysterious sounds in an abandoned zoo with ghost hunter Ernie Hudson.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;accessibility: &amp;ldquo;This room is not accessible and not suitable for physically impaired players.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;warnings: &amp;ldquo;Not suitable for people with a peanut allergy.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;note: &amp;ldquo;Both &amp;lsquo;Ernie Hudson&amp;rsquo; games can be played independently and do not require any prior knowledge.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A new case for ghost hunter Ernie Hudson and his team. The investigation will take you to the abandoned Sandy Bay zoo. It is said that strange noises can be heard between the cages and gates at night. A case for real professionals! Do you have the courage to take on the case? The story is also told using radio play elements. Look forward to various locations, countless effects and lots of surprises.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guschis seedy Cellar</title>
      <link>https://example.org/guschis-seedy-cellar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/guschis-seedy-cellar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;note-this-game-is-only-available-in-german&#34;&gt;shortTitle: &amp;ldquo;Guschis seedy Cellar&amp;rdquo;&#xA;players: &amp;ldquo;4-8 people&amp;rdquo;&#xA;idealPlayers: &amp;ldquo;ideal for 5 players&amp;rdquo;&#xA;minAge: &amp;ldquo;from 18 years&amp;rdquo;&#xA;shortDescription: &amp;ldquo;Break into an 80s Kiez bar to find 30,000 Marks in this adults-only adventure.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;accessibility: &amp;ldquo;This room is not accessible.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;warnings: &amp;ldquo;Tis room is not accessible&amp;rdquo;&#xA;note: &amp;ldquo;This game is only available in German&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our absolute classic! This game takes you into the red light milieu of the 80s. . It&amp;rsquo;s about sex, and drugs, and money! Your aim is to break into the notorious neighbourhood pub/brothel – &amp;lsquo;Guschi&amp;rsquo;s Seedy Cellar&amp;rsquo;, struggle through various torture chambers and porn cabins, whilst searching for 30,000 Deutsch Marks. This experience (like many on the Reeperbahn), is only for visitors over 18 years of age. Some exceptions may be agreed, if you contact us in advance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malvinis Legacy</title>
      <link>https://example.org/malvinis-legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/malvinis-legacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;note-&#34;&gt;shortTitle: &amp;ldquo;Malvinis Legacy&amp;rdquo;&#xA;players: &amp;ldquo;3-8 people&amp;rdquo;&#xA;idealPlayers: &amp;ldquo;ideal for 4-5 players&amp;rdquo;&#xA;minAge: &amp;ldquo;from 14 years&amp;rdquo;&#xA;shortDescription: &amp;ldquo;Search for the Book of Immortality in a magician&amp;rsquo;s enchanted chamber.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;accessibility: &amp;ldquo;This room is accessible.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;warnings: &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&#xA;note: &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Visit the most magical escape room &amp;lsquo;Malvinis Legacy&amp;rsquo; in Hamburg and be enchanted by the mysterious stage magician Edgar Malvini. Enter his enchanted chamber and solve the mystical puzzles on the edge of the occult. What lies behind Malvini&amp;rsquo;s legacy – just a few clever tricks or real magic? Embark on the search for the legendary Book of Immortality to uncover the secret of Malvini&amp;rsquo;s legacy. Immerse yourself in the world of the magician, search the chamber for clues, and combine your conclusions to shed light on the darkness. But be careful not to be led astray by the magic&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Phantom Island</title>
      <link>https://example.org/phantom-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/phantom-island/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;note-&#34;&gt;shortTitle: &amp;ldquo;The Phantom Island&amp;rdquo;&#xA;players: &amp;ldquo;2-6 people&amp;rdquo;&#xA;idealPlayers: &amp;ldquo;ideal for 3-4 players&amp;rdquo;&#xA;minAge: &amp;ldquo;from 14 years&amp;rdquo;&#xA;shortDescription: &amp;ldquo;Explore a shipwrecked sailor&amp;rsquo;s shelter on a mysterious, not-so-idyllic island.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;accessibility: &amp;ldquo;This room is not barrier-free&amp;rdquo;&#xA;warnings: &amp;ldquo;Stroboscope effects are used.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;note: &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For bone collectors and treasure hunters! This escape game has been extensively renewed in 2019 and takes you to the mysterious Phantom Island – into the moldy shelter of a long-dead sailor. The poor soul was shipwrecked several hundred years ago on the godforsaken Phantom island and struggled to survive. You are now the first team of intrepid specialists to observe this weird and spooky island. But beware! The island is not as idyllic as it appears.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
